Jai Hind friends, please read the disclaimer.
I am not a SEBI registered advisor
friends.
In this video we are going to talk about 13 dividend paying stocks.
Some companies are giving special dividends.
Some are also giving final dividend and some
interim dividend.  The
first company that will come to us will be Excel
Solution India.  We see it trading at a current price of ₹1500.   It is a
company with a market cap of ₹200 crore.   It's a
great company.  Look at the fundamentals, check
your operating profit, ROC, ROE, everything is
looking better.  Now this
company is giving us a final
dividend of ₹40.  Last time also the final
dividend was given of ₹40 only but the interim
dividend given by the company was ₹50.  The
company has fixed its record date as 24 October 2025.
And let us tell you that
23rd October is going to be the last date for purchasing it.
So you guys please
see this.  It is a good dividend.  A big
dividend is a good dividend.  The next company
is Indian Railway Finance Corporation
Limited IRFC is
trading at 124 current price.  It is a
big company with a market cap of ₹1600 crores.
It has a dividend yield of 1.3% per year.
Its fundamentals are also clearly visible.
This company is
giving a dividend of ₹1.5, yes friends, ₹1.5.
It has also
fixed its record date ex-date as 24 October 2025 and 23
October will be the last date for purchasing
for this also.  Please note it.  The next
share that will come is signed at ₹171, its current
price.  When it was announced, I had
told you that its dividend
is also a company with a market cap of Rs 13000 crore, it
gives a dividend of 2.2%, but its yield on year basis is around 2.5%.
This time the company is also giving interim dividend at ₹16 per equity share.  Last
time the interim dividend was ₹12.  So
dividend, this time the company has
increased the interim dividend.  The remaining final dividend of
₹14 was given.  24 October 2025, this company has
fixed its record date and ex-date
and its last date for purchasing will also be
23 October 2025, so two-three more days are
left, you guys should check it out, right? If we
talk about the next share, the next share will come,
LTI MTRED is
seen trading at ₹605 current price, it
is a giant company with a market capital of ₹166000 crores.   It's a
great company.  This company is also
giving interim dividend.  At ₹22 per equity share, the
company had last paid an entry dividend of ₹20 and the final
dividend is ₹45.  The
company has fixed its record date as 24 October 2025
and the
last date for purchasing it will also be 23 October 2025.
Okay, right?  The next share will be
our Thair Technology.  This
company is also giving bonus.  Please pay attention.   I have
told you.  I am running a list here right now.
You guys please see.  I am not driving.  I have
made a video and told you the
list of 37 bonus and speed, you guys should watch it,
subscribe to the channel,
like the video and also set the bell icon to all.
Shares worth ₹144, a
company with a market cap of 6000-6500 crores, this is also a
good company, you guys can check it as per your wish,
this company is giving dividend,
first of all, as per equity share of ₹7, it will
give a dividend of ₹7 on 24 October 2025, the
company has fixed the record date ex-date,
23 October is going to be the last date for purchasing.
For this also which you can see.
Along with this, I have also written the company here in the ratio of 2:1.  It is
giving bonus in big letters in the ratio of 2:1.  For
every one share, two shares will be
given as bonus and the total will be three shares
here.  You will see.  Record
date X date has not arrived.  I will update when it arrives.
And to get the latest updates, you
can also join the channel membership.
Between 9:00 and 3:00.
Friends, we will talk about the next share here.  So
our next share will come here.
Which one is it brother?  It is not opening.  Yes
HDB Finance Services Limited current
price is ₹730.  It has a dividend yield of 0.27%.  It is a
company with a market cap of ₹0000 crore.  The fundamentals are
neutral.  You guys please see.   According to
me, this company is giving dividend for the first time at ₹2 per
equity share.
October 24 is its record tax date
and October 23 is going to be the last date for purchasing.  Please
note this also.   The
next share will be ours.
Vari Energy LED is a good company,
it has a five star rating from my side, its
current price is ₹3535, there has been a decline of 2%
in the last trading session,
this is a company with a market cap of ₹1 lakh crore and
its dividend yield is very modest, very
small and the company has also given a small dividend, as per
equity share at ₹2, the company has
given dividend on 24 October 2025, its
report date is ex-date and 23 October is
going to be the last date for buying, it is
also good for this, the next company will come for
us, here Dalmia Bharat
Limited has a
current price of 2245.
This company also has a market cap of ₹42,000 crore.  Let's say the sugar sector is like this.  The
company is also giving interim dividend at ₹4 per equity share.
Last time also the company had given an intimation dividend of ₹4 and the time before that
also it was ₹4.  The
remaining final dividend of ₹-5 is
given to us by this company which you
can see.  After that, if we
look here at the report date ex-date, then the record
date here has been fixed by the company as 24 October 2025
and the last date for purchasing is going to be
23 October 2025.   Please
note it.  See the next share.
Our next stock is ICICI LBRD LED.
₹000 is the current price trading at.
This company also has a market cap of ₹1 lakh crore.
It is giving an interim dividend of ₹6.5.  It was worth ₹6.50
and last time also I had paid ₹5.50.  Before that, the
company has been continuously increasing the interim dividend by ₹5.  The
final dividend was also increased from ₹6 to ₹7
in June 2025.  So the
company is also increasing the final dividend.  If we look at its yield
here, the company is giving a yield of 0.6%.
Its record date is 23 October.  Do you
understand?  October 23 is the record date.
So now just call tomorrow as the date for last purchase
or on 21st when Muhurat
trading will take place, you can call that day also as the last
trading session.  So there
is very little time left.  Go and see this.
Limited by doing something on Yoon.
Its name is a little different.  Yuns is Yunparts Ltd.  The
name of the company is India Limited,
you can see the current price and its trade price is ₹526, the name of the company is
Uniparts India.  That's correct.
And if we look at this
here friends, the current price
is 526.  It is a company with a market cap of ₹2300 crores.  It
gives good dividend.  It is
offering a dividend yield of 2.7%.  This company is
giving us a dividend of ₹22.52 or ₹22.50.  23rd October is its record
date ex-date and you can say tomorrow or
day after tomorrow is going to be its
last date to buy, so note this also, the
next share of ours will come, K
India is a small company, a
company with a market cap of Rs 765 crore, this company is also
giving dividend to us and if we
see its dividend yield, it is good
brother, it is a dividend of about 4.8%, brother
its yield is tremendous and this company is also giving us entry at ₹5 per
equity share
and its record date ex-
date is 23rd October 2025 and
consider its last date to buy as tomorrow or day after tomorrow.  If you
liked the video, please like and
subscribe to the channel.  See you in the
next video